Now I've taken weakness as my ally
I can fly to the highest heights
If I would just stop here
all I've lost would lose its luster
If you were lost out somewhere
at the same time my heart is shaken
Id have no way to find you
your kindness, or even your strength
I know
It's time for the dawn!
My peak performance
I'll blow straight past in a blast, yeah
You'll be left frozen with laughs
The days of pain left in the past, let's hope
As I make foes of the world
I'm bracing myself upon shaking legs, yeah
Just keep me going for a few more steps
Now, this is the comeback, the time to awaken is now
Winding our story's clock back
just a little bit...
Here we find what once was the final resting place of
Kozuki Oden and his retainers, including Kin'emon:
The ruins of Oden Castle, in Kuri.
Kaido's Blast Breath left nothing
of the ruins in its wake.
It was there that Oden constructed
his first castle upon becoming Daimyo of Kuri.
Daimyo!
Luffy!
Hey there!
Luffytaro-san!
Yo! What's got the
whole gang comin' here?
We have come to tell
Oden-sama of our victory.
There are other matters we want
to discuss with him as well.
Why's you-gara here, though?
I'm here to see Oden!
I am certain Oden-sama is overjoyed
to meet with the Savior of Wano!
Ya really think so?
Oden-sama...
It is thanks to Luffytaro-dono and the others here
that we were able to fell Orochi and Kaido,
and return the Land of Wano
to her people.
We, together with our new Shogun,
Momonosuke-sama,
swear to you that we shall restore
our country to what it once was,
a place where all can live in peace.
How I wish Ashura and Izo
could join us here...
They are here.
Within our bosoms,
alongside Oden-sama.
Mmm, true that.
Certainly they must be hosting
a grand feast in the afterlife!
Prrrmeow meowmeow!
Oden cooked by Oden-sama
was the most delicious thing in the world!
Ah, yes... I do recall its taste,
and how we all used to share in it.
Aye. It tasted even better
after training with Oden-sama.
Sounds neat!
Wish I coulda had some!
Me, too!
Let's ask Sanji-kun
to cook it for us sometime!
We ought to stock up on
ingredients for it then!
Totally! We're gonna buy tons!
Luffy-dono...
Are you departing?
Yeah.
We would like to take this opportunity...
...to once again offer
our most sincere gratitude!
Whoooa?!
C'mon, cut that out!
We're friends, ain't we?
Luffy!
Carrot!
You're leaving already?
You can't, you can't, you just can't!
I don't wanna say goodbye to Nami, either!
Dun wanna, dun wanna, I dun wanna!
Carrot...
Hey, what's botherin' ya?
We're going back home...
...to the Mokomo Dukedom!
I'm gonna be defending our home
along with Wanda and everyone else!
Miyagi, Tristan...
Thank you both!
Thank you for all
you've taught me about medicine!
Dr. Chopper, take care of yourself!
If I do recall, Carrot-san,
you stowed away aboard the Sunny
because you wanted to see the sea, no?
Well, how'd you like it?
It was only the best adventure ever!
I got to see islands I never knew existed,
and met some nice people!
There were lotsa scary moments,
but I feel I'm a little stronger than I used to be.
That's why the adventure
I had with you all...
...is something I'll treasure
for the rest of my life!
Lemme have one last garchu
for the road!
Garchu!
It was super fun chatting and having a blast
with you in the women's quarters, Nami!
Yeah, it was the best!
You too, Chobro!
That tickles!
I'm happy too, Carrot!
Garchu!
Oh, yeah! I saw Zoro on my way here.
m
Zoro, ya say?
Go on, it's on me.
Whatcha doin'?
Thought I'd share a round with him.
I'll pour it for ya!
You the one that left the flowers?
Eh? Yup!
Big Sis helped me.
Ah, here you are, Zorojuro-san.
Yeah.
May you both rest in peace.
Once they finish that big, nice temple,
I'll come to see you every day, Daddy!
That way, you won't be lonely, right?
Right, right?
Your being here means the time has come
for you to depart, does it not?
Yeah.
It shall be lonely without you.
I shall have to bid farewell
to my father's beloved Enma, then?
Guess so.
I ain't givin' it back.
Aye, of course not!
"Enma, able to rend even
the deepest depths of hell", huh?
Oden must've been
one helluva guy...
'Cause he'd completely
tamed this thing, hadn't he?
Yet you, Zorojuro-san,
liberated our nation...
.... through your
skillful wielding of Enma.
Nah, not skilled enough.
To me, it looks as if Enma is rejoicing...
...at having found its new master.
I... will become stronger.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
The hell's this, Fraguy?!
Yo, boss! Somethin' outta place?
Damn right, there is!
Huuuh?! Ain't no way there is!
Damn moron!
Ya asked me to check out
where ya made repairs,
and I was doin' just that, numbskull!
It's per-fect-ion,
ya ingrate!
You coulda left me
at least one spot t'fix,
ya absolute buffoon!
Oh, excuse me for lettin' ya down!
So she's all repaired
and in tip-top shape?
He's definitely the
Straw Hats' shipwright!
Later, ya total dunce!
And stay healthy,
ya blitherin' idiot!
What're ya yappin' about?!
Heeey, done yet?
Yes, sir! Yes, yes!
I'm on my way, sir!
Right, sorry to have kept you waiting!
No prob.
How do you feel about this?
Eh?
I think it's a great fit for you, sir!
Usohachi-san, you're cool!
It's the most handsome
man in all of Wano!
Look this way!
Need something from me, m'lady?
I love it!
Whoa, uh, I mean,
not really...
Oh, say no more!
I hear you, I hear you...
This color would look good on you, too!
Neh?
Usohachi-san!
Hey there, ladykiller!
The color red was just made for him!
He's sooo hot!
Don't go fallin' in love
with me, now!
No, absolutely not!
Heeh?
All I'm after is plain black cloth!
And a crapload of it!
Huh? Black cloth?
For what might you need so much, sir?
Uh? Well, uh, that's, uh...
Don't tell anyone, but...
WhaaaaFor that?!
I shall provide you with
the finest available!
Right on!
Countin' on you!
Right, then!
That's it for today!
Thank you for the lesson.
Sangoro's Specialty Soba!
It's so good!
I love your Specialty Soba!
Thank you for the meal.
Come again!
How's it taste?
It is the best I've ever had!
Good to hear.
Oh, Chuji!
How're ya doin', little guy?
Coochie coochie...
Something the matter?
Oh? Oh, nothing...
Come to think of it...
I have yet to properly express my thanks
to you for saving me at Onigashima.
Don't mention it!
Just doing the right thing.
Ah, will you be coming back here again?
Because eating your soba, Sangoro-san, gives me
the strength to keep working hard, day after day!
I'm happy just hearing that!
But I've gotta set off soon.
Sangoro-san, I...!
Mr. Soba Chef?
Badumbadumbadum!
Could I trouble you for a bowl?
Robin-chwan!
Thanks for comin' bwy!
I'd like mine served hot, please.
I'm on it, Robin-chwan!
Ah, if I might have the same?
Sure
Great job, everyone!
Go on, rest awhile
and have some oshiruko!
Always appreciate
the refreshments, O-Tsuru-san!
Let's dig in!
Looks good!
It's oshiruko!
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Dun worry 'bout it!
Down the hatch!
Yuu-uu-um!
Nom, nom!
Thank you for the food!
O-Tsuru-san's oshiruko is the bestest!
Ya think so?
Eat the mochi, too!
Okay!
It'sh shoguud!
Eat 'til ya burst, Tama!
Mmhmm!
What's up, Tama?
When I think about havin'
to say goodbye to you here,
I get a lump in my throat...
First Ace,
an' now you, Big Bro...
All the people
I love leave me...
Tama...
You know that time ya gave me
that precious rice of yours?
I ain't ever gonna forget that!
Then I ain't gonna forget 'bout
you or yer crew, Big Bro!
Deal!
Kay, gotta get goin'.
Okey dokey!
We'll meet again, Tama!
Big Bro, thank yoooou!
I'mma be like you 'n Ace...
an' get stronger, you'll see!
And now, our story
returns to the present...
Luffy! We're ready to set sail!
Gotcha!
But are you really sure
about leaving like this?
We didn't say goodbye
to Momo-chan and Kin'emon.
Oh yeah, you're right.
We don't gotta go that far.
Pretty cold, comin' outta you, Mossbrain.
Shut it, Swirlybrow.
But of all the people in Wano,
they shared in our adventures the most.
Quite, it seems a bit sad
to part ways like this.
Luffy, what do you wanna do?
It'll be fine.
He'll come!
"Time's up'
Someone said again, with a laugh
Fine then, hide-and-seek playtime...
...is over
Let's go, come on (We can see it soon)
Let your heart beat out
and things will change (We can see it soon)
Grow strong, you have time
Raise up that dream
The overflowing loneliness can't sustain me alone
We were so free in our younger days
What a dumb dream
...to live
Shining a light on uncharted ways
Get on our feet and try
Let's see the ends of the world together
Together, we can go and fly